http://www.britishconnemaras.co.uk/privacy-policy

0845 604 969001420 89114
(Contact Us)
HomeBCPSThe SocietyAbout the BCPSBreed StandardBCPS CouncilThe Connemara ChronicleSafeguardingWelfareConnemara SocietiesCBPSICCPSMembershipsMembership & FeesRenewals200 ClubBreeding & OwningBreedingBreed StandardBreeding StatisticsInspectionsInfo for Stallion OwnersStallionsPremiumsPremiums GeneralPremium MaresPremium StallionsRegistrationsNew RegistrationsPassportsTransfersIrish TransfersOwnership TransferHWSDSummaryDetailConnemara DatabasesBCPS DatabaseCBPS DatabaseShows & CompetitionsShowsBreed ShowNorthern Breed ShowRegional ShowsTam O' Shanter QualifiersDressage ChampionshipEventingEventing SeriesEventing Series QualifiersPerformance DayPerformance Award SchemeSummary and ResultsShowing AdviceRules For ShowingJudgesShow AffiliationShow Entry SystemShow MaintenanceAdvertisementsUK AdvertisementsPonies for SalePonies for LoanPonies WantedStallionsAdvertise HereGeneral InformationOnline AdvertisementsBanner AdvertisingAdvertising LoginGoto LoginRegionsNewsCalendarShop
MENU
HomeBCPSThe SocietyAbout the BCPSBreed StandardBCPS CouncilThe Connemara ChronicleSafeguardingWelfareConnemara SocietiesCBPSICCPSMembershipsMembership & FeesRenewals200 ClubBreeding & OwningBreedingBreed StandardBreeding StatisticsInspectionsInfo for Stallion OwnersStallionsPremiumsPremiums GeneralPremium MaresPremium StallionsRegistrationsNew RegistrationsPassportsTransfersIrish TransfersOwnership TransferHWSDSummaryDetailConnemara DatabasesBCPS DatabaseCBPS DatabaseShows & CompetitionsShowsBreed ShowNorthern Breed ShowRegional ShowsTam O' Shanter QualifiersDressage ChampionshipEventingEventing SeriesEventing Series QualifiersPerformance DayPerformance Award SchemeSummary and ResultsShowing AdviceRules For ShowingJudgesShow AffiliationShow Entry SystemShow MaintenanceAdvertisementsUK AdvertisementsPonies for SalePonies for LoanPonies WantedStallionsAdvertise HereGeneral InformationOnline AdvertisementsBanner AdvertisingAdvertising LoginGoto LoginRegionsNewsCalendarShop
BCPS DatabaseCBPS DatabasePonies for SaleStallionsRenewals
Privacy PolicyData Protection Contact
The contact details for the Secretary for any data protection queries are as follows:
Email: secretary@britishconnemaras.co.uk 2.1.2. Tel: +44 0845 604 9690 (10:00am to 04:00pm)
CLICK HERE FOR OUR FULL PRIVACY AND POLICY DOCUMENT
Visitors to the British Connemara Pony Society website – Cookie Policy
About cookies:A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server 8.1.2. Cookies may be either "persistent" cookies or "session" cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closedCookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.We use cookies to monitor how people use the BCPS website and for the following reasons:authentication - we use cookies to identify you when you visit our website and as you navigate our website.status - we use cookies to help us to determine if you are logged into our website.advertising - we do not use cookies to help us to display advertisements that will be relevant to youanalysis - we use Google cookies to help us to analyse the use and performance of our website and services. Cookies used for this purpose are specified by GoogleCookie information is held on your browser and you can amend your browser settings at any time. However, please be aware that blocking or deleting all cookies will affect the usability of the BCPS website.Google Analytics
This website collects information via Google Analytics. Google Analytics mainly uses first-party cookies to report on user interactions on your website. These cookies are used to store non-personally identifiable information. Browsers do not share first-party cookies across domains.
If you don't want their your data collected with Google Analytics, you can install the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. To opt-out of Analytics for the web, visit the Google Analytics opt-out page and install the add-on for your browser. For more details on installing and uninstalling the add-on, please see the relevant help resources for your specific browser.
The Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on does not prevent data from being sent to the website itself, or to other web analytics services.
BCPS Terms and Conditions |
BCPS Privacy Policy
Registered No: 01006107
Registered Charity No: 262765
The British Connemara Pony Society is a company Limited by Guarantee
Designed/Hosted by Biziserve
©British Connemara Pony Society
© Copyright Notice: No photographs displayed on this website may be used or reproduced in any way whatsoever. CD&P Act 1988
This website uses Cookies. By continuing to use this website, you consent to our use of these cookies.
More information can be found on our  Privacy Policy Page.
x
